alison lamb

contact

✓ alisonlamba@gmail.com

914.645.8586

(a) @alilambop

alisonlambdesigns.com

skills

- Adobe Creative Suite
- Art Direction + Branding
- Marketing Design + Strategy
- Catalog + Book Design
- Web UI/UX Design
- Presentation Design
- LMS Design and Theory
- Social media design
- Color Theory
- CMS and Content mamt.
- Microsoft Office

education

Fashion Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Fine Arts

La Sorbonne Paris IV

profile

The role of a graphic designer is not an entirely creative one. I view my work as problem resolution through visual communication. I sift through concepts, ideas, sketches, and research with you to help identify the true focus of the project. From there, we can cleanly, efficiently, and effectively build the story.



contact

experience

Gro Intelligence /// January 2020 - Present, New York, NY

Senior Visual Designer

- Presentation design (google slides)
- DSM generation and management
- Brand codification and assertion across all platforms
- Key Contact between Design and Development team
- UI + Email Design

Alison Lamb Designs /// May 2017 - January 2020, New York, NY

Creative Director, personal freelance venture

- Marketing and Presentation design
- Catalog Design, Vector Art design
- B2C + B2B graphic design and support
- Brand management, detvelopment and assertion
- Content generation and management
- Material sourcing, marketing schedule management and financial projections
- Web UI / UX design and development management

WeWork /// April 2019 - November 2019, New York, NY

Lead Presentation Designer, Sales Training + Enablement Department

- Head graphic designer for the Sales Training Department
- Generation of presentation templates, booklets, graphic assets, learning tools and all training collateral needed
- Learner psychology analysis + interpretation
- Working in tandem with learning engineers to communicate complex LMS and learning programs to hundreds of new hires globally per month

De La Vega Designs /// October 2017 - January 2019, Brooklyn, NY

Creative Marketing + Design Consultant

- Brand management and development
- Catalog and lookbook design for print
- Marketing graphic designer / email marketing designer
- Web UI / UX design and management

Roll & Hill /// December 2016 - May 2017, Brooklyn, NY

Assistant Creative Director

- Brand management
- Art Direction for branding photo shoots (on location Mexico, NYC)
- Email Marketing design and implementation

Holland & Sherry Interiors /// June 2014 - November 2016, New York, NY Marketing Manager, Creative Director

- Development & direction of marketing schedule within an annual budget of \$300,000
- Head designer for all graphic design needs (internal and external uses)
- Art Direction for collateral content photo shoots (on location NYC, Europe)
- Email Marketing design and implementation



✓ alisonlamba@gmail.com

914.645.8586

🙀 alisonlambdesigns.com